Long ago, Gold Roger,
the King of Pirates, obtained
everything the world had to offer,
and his dying roads drove
countless souls to the seas.
You want my treasure?
You can have it!
I left everything in one place.
Now you just have to find it!
And thus a new age began.
This is the time known
as the Great Pirate Era!
Oh, I'm done playing
through with the waiting,
either will I'm feeling alive,
look out below, wake up sunshine,
here we go.
Raise your flag up high,
hail a brand new dawn.
Blaze across the sky, time
to journey on, on your mark.
Come aboard with me.
We're on Earth, a legendary!.
If you can show your breath?
Then we'll make some waves!.
We run our daunted!.
Ain't no beginners!.
Cause if you're wanted?
Then you're a winner!.
For we are on the cruise!.
And freedom is the only rule!.
Fearless night and day!.
Cause that's just our way!.
Find one piece!.
I'll be the first!.
I've heard it be so bad just at first!.
It's all this real!.
It must be cause my hand's on the wheel!.
I'm done playing, feel it's waiting!.
In the world I'm feeling alive!.
But I'll be loud!.
Wake up sunshine, here we go!.
We have come so far!.
Gotta make it to the end!.
Whatever danger we find,
no one ever left behind!.
I've always got your back, my friend!.
Sail on shoreward, keep marching forward!.
Dreaming from the very first
day, I'd make my name!.
And don't you know that
dream hasn't changed!.
I'm done playing through with the wave!.
In the world I'm feeling
alive, look out below!.
Wake up, sunshine!.
Wake up, sunshine, here we go!
We go!
Wait, that's odd.
Where did that stripey fellow go?
I've completely lost sight of him.
Imbecile.
I'm right here.
But you'll be dead long
before you can notice.
Now take this.
Amoplage carpet!
Why did it sound like
the ground was talking?
Oh, that's a good aim.
See ya!
You've fallen into my trap.
Little did you know that was my
weapon-destroying technique, body sword crush.
Now the tip of your sword has crumbled.
It's worthless.
No, I stabbed you.
He really thinks he can play it off.
Your arrogance will only lead to
your Davy - uh, lead to your defeat!
What?
I lost him again!
How does he do that?
Hidden flail.
66 now!
I've learned something
in these past two years.
I've come to an understanding about the
true nature of the revive, revive fruit.
When most people die,
their body is left behind while their
soul continues on to the next world.
But my soul is different.
In accordance with the power of my devil
fruit, it has been tempered like iron.
Radiating with strength,
it maintains its hold in this realm
with a presence that is palpable.
That soul resonates through
the strings of my instruments.
Rock and roll, screaming
from another dimension.
Mesmerized by its melodies.
The listeners dance their
way into a land of illusions.
But when my soul flutters
away from this old body?
It is no mere apparition!
It can be seen as surely
as my rattling bones.
I did it!
POPPED HIS HEAD RIGHT OFF HIS BODY NECK!
I KILLED A Straw Hat!
I'M FINE.
You can chop me up as much as you'd like,
for it is neither flesh nor
organs that bind me to this world.
So what is it that gives
me life, you might ask?
IT'S MY SOOOOOOOM!
I killed him so hard it
brought him back to life.
Man, I'm good!
Are you for real?
Is it starting to sink in yet?
Keep it up.
But none of your attacks can
damage these bones and mine.
I'm already dead and you're
not going to kill me twice.
Also, this blade I wield
is like none other,
sharpened by the Long-Armed tribe
and granted up a fitting name.
Soul Solid, engrave that
title upon your heart!
With a single soulful slash,
it'll freeze you with the frigid air
creeping from the land of the dead.
As its icy grip claims you,
gaze upon its bitter blade.
Nice, Brook!
That's awesome!
I guess I'd better step it up.
The whole crew's looking good,
showing off those skills they
learned for the new world.
Yeah, yeah!
It's real sweet to hear how highly
you think of all your friends.
But don't you worry,
since I'm such a nice guy,
I'll make sure to drown
all of you together!
Special attack!
Fireball cutter!
Go!
Green Star!
Bouncing faster!
I think it's safe to say I found
the weak link in the Straw Hat crew.
All those shots and you couldn't
even hit me a single time.
Might want to stay put, mole shark.
I'm a cookie cutter shark, jerk.
Whatever.
I hope you enjoy the trap I set for you.
Just lie down and give up.
You can't stop the Noah now.
And you'll watch every one
of your friends perish?
Hell no!
I'm putting you down!
Illusions of grandeur!
Now, die!
Second gear! Armament!
Now, come, come!
Come on, fight your arm off!
Red Hawk!
You did it, Moshi!
Wake me Hachi!
Let's get to the Noah! Right!
Full speed ahead! Okay!
I refuse to run! Are you insane?
The Noah's right above us! I know that.
I'm not stupid.
But this reminds me.
It makes me think of another
pirate who fought to protect us.
It happened when I was a kid.
Twenty years ago.
I even recall you being
there. You remember?
There was one other human
our kingdom revered.
Hell of a hole we got.
Get back here.
What the hell?
You in the mood to die or something?
No way!
What's he doing here?
And why is he siding with the fishmen?
Neptune helped me out of a jam
one time back when we were young,
and we pledged friendship
over cups of sake.
Please don't kill me! I promise!
We'll never kidnap
mermaids or fish men again.
You want to mess with my friend's country
then you face the consequences you snot!
You listen up this island
is under my protection.
You're talking about
whitebeard that guy was a
living legend you trust
the Straw Hats that much?
Don't get me wrong i i
don't even like humans
honestly and this is
our kingdom not theirs.
But they our minds were made up as soon
as we got to the plaza with jimbe's help.
We were gonna save this island
leave it to me and my crew.
That's what friends are
for right the things that
straw had said and they're
risking their lives?
Let's go!
I can breathe!
If he's this tough, his
bounty would be high!
You humans can be so
arrogant it amazes me!
You're more likely to get yourselves
killed than admit how weak you are!
So I'll have to beat
some humility into you.
Look, I'm kind of in a hurry.
We've finished this up already!
If you think you can, be my cat!
Weepy Hachi, get out of here! Wait!
This time, Jiu-Jitsu!
Water Hut!
Shut that mouth!
I messed it up!
I'll die!
Third gear!
Armament!
Hardening!
How much does it take?
Insolent fool!
Come, come!
Help me, come!
Kill them all.
They've forsaken their
brightest fish, man.
They deserve to pay the price.
Ahhhhhhhhhhhhhh!
Come, come, come!
Come, come, come, come!
He did it!
Go ahead, beat him! Finally!
Heart is down!
This is the end!
Everyone on the island is doomed!
Run for it!
Who?
Why, Zeal?
The island's gonna get crushed!
Please, let us go!
Don't you dare fall for it.
You know the power our captain has.
He was chosen by heaven!
He could never be beaten by
some measly, pathetic human!
But, I mean, we're not getting nothing
if the Noah destroys this place!
Death is only another form of revenge.
And we will die for our hatred of
humans our flesh and blood will be
remembered as a tragedy and the grudge
against humans will grow ever stronger.
We may fall, but thousands more will
stand up to take revenge in our name!
Oh, goody?
There you are.
You're all insane, not just Captain
Heart, but all of you officers too.
Blame the humans!
They're the ones who made us this way!
Don't run!
Take that rage of yours and let
it loose on all of humanity!
They deserve your hate. Look around.
Do you know what they've done to us?
They're the ones behind every
disaster the fish had up met!
Is all that stuff you're saying true?
Are humans really that bad? Huh?
No way, that's ridiculous.
I mean, sure,
humans have done plenty of awful things,
especially when you look
at their history with...
That's enough.
Madam Charlie!
You can see what's happening
with your own eyes.
Just look, on the ground, and in the sky.
The humans are fighting against
the new fishman pirates, for us.
What about that guy is
he human their crew is
a bit strange but the
important thing is what
They're doing you must
see things for yourself
that's the only way to
understand the truth
No matter what you've heard in the past you
must look at today with an objective eye
Even if you refuse to fight to the death
and try to run, I'll kill you myself.
Your hatred of humans won't be waiting.
Huh?
They're your own people.
That's how you treat them?
I almost died.
Thank you so much, Mr.
Skeleton Mask.
You again, huh?
You've never died, so don't talk
like you know anything about it.
Tied to leave your hate behind?
That's just absurd!
There's nothing left when you die.
The only things left
behind are your bones!
The guy knows what he's talking about!
Thank you!
If there's one kind of
person I don't like,
it's someone who doesn't
value the lives of others.
I can't even stand their smell.
And I don't have a nose to smell them!
You and your friends are the ones
who don't value the lives of others.
I bet you all think you're being bold
and selfish by staying here to fight.
But every last one of you humans are
gonna die when the Noah hits the island!
Although I'm still not sure
whether you're human or not.
I can promise you that
one of these days our
Captain Luffy will become
the king of the pirates.
He is a man who keeps his
word no matter the cost.
So if he says that no harm will come to
the people here, then no harm will come.
I believe in him no matter what.
so that ship will never touch this island.
And now it's time for me
to step up and do my part.
That means I won't let you
disappear before my eyes again,
even though I have no eyes to speak of!
Whoa, how about this?
Impressed yet?
Oh, sure, that's pretty damn big.
Yeah, impressive stuff.
Ha, ha, ha!
Not so!
Well then, do you want to
wrap this up now, Jinbei?
Yeah, it's about time!
Huh?
Hey, not fair.
You've destroyed both of my swords.
How could I win a sword
fight if I don't have swords?
Not my problem.
All right, I'm going balls out.
This new special move is going to
take you down in a single shot.
One, two, and on the third step,
it's all over. Think I'm kidding?
Just try me.
What kind of moron do you take me for?
I'm calling you out on your stupid bluff.
You're a weakling and
you'll always be a weakling.
You know, I used to lie about
this kind of stuff all the time.
But now it doesn't really
matter if you believe me or not.
Because I know I'm the real deal.
Holy crap!
What is that monster?
Yeah!
Where did that thing come from?
Whoa, did he?
No, not again!
Huh?
That runt?
How'd he get so big?
Whoa, pal! Easy! Easy!
Calm down, Chopper!
You can't lose control like before!
Huh?
Don't worry, Usopp.
I know what I'm doing.
Chopper, are you sure
you're okay over there?
Oh yeah, I got it all under control.
With just one rumble ball, I can
fight in this form for three minutes.
Plus, I don't pass out at the
end or anything like that.
Now you guys don't have to
look out for me so much.
Don't sell yourself short if
you can do this kind of stuff
whenever you want you're gonna
be the one looking out for us!
Flattery will get you nowhere, buddy.
Doesn't work on me. Ha!
Nope, not at all
That's creepy.
Now you've really made me angry!
I don't care how big you are
all it takes is one good docent.
and you're out of here!
Dosing all you want?
Sorry, but I don't plan on going anywhere.
Now, bring it on!
Nice going.
Yeah!
You think you can just chat it up with
your friend in the middle of a fight?
You're lucky I don't gnaw
straight through you.
I don't know why your Straw Hat pals bother
putting up with dead weight like you.
I'm gonna do my favor and
put you out of your misery.
You're welcome to try but first I
want to show you something cool.
Pay attention you're about to see
a magic trick you'll never forget.
A special move if that's your game
I've got plenty of those myself.
Maybe the squid spear didn't
work but I've got another
weapon that'll Don't cut through
anything you can throw at me,
hee!
Say hello to the Lightbrite spear!
It's powerful enough to cut
a hole through your cockpit!
This battle will be over in one
shot, but it'll be won by me, hee!
That does look pretty sweet!
But if I'm being honest, it's still way
less ultimate than my ultimate weapon!
You're squid out of luck now, dude!
What's a swordman without his swords?
What should I do?
You're just going to croak
like a frog. I'm done.
Waste of time.
Wrap this up, you said?
Not till I'm good and ready.
You think I got all puffed up just
to deal with a loser like you?
Quit dreaming!
You know all I got to do is
roll around this plaza a few
times and all your friends will
be smooshed flat as pancakes!
This is my space you washed
up pile of bones take one step
inside this circle and you'll
be dead all over again I promise
your move
I'm terribly sorry, but I've already made
my way inside the circle and cut you.
Also, as a fair warning,
this will be cold.
When did you get in here?
Song of Scratches.
Blizzard Slice.
And now, a haiku.
A blood-chilling wind howls
from the land of the dead
Gotcha!
Ah!
What is this?
My queen star, human drake technique?
Those plants have arms
and leg-shaped roots that
attack and latch onto
whatever flies over them!
Good luck with that.
Now what?
Green Star Trampolia.
It's pretty self-explanatory. Anyway,
now that you've been
catapulted into the sky,
there's not much you can
do to defend yourself.
Here goes Green Star.
I don't care about you, dumb dog.
I'll rip it to shreds.
I wouldn't.
See that red bulb on its nose?
If you attack, that thing will release a
devastating shockwave three meters wide.
Like this.
That's what?
Awesome, right?
Dosan!
Glamsan!
Slamsan!
Better watch out or you'll get hit by
the dosanest dosan that ever dosered!
Popper a hammer!
It's mine!
It's our fault!
It's roguesome.
Eka, eka, eka!
Too bad.
You won't make dried squid out of me!
Franky!
Eka, eka, eka!
Radical me!
It's got a laser beam too.
And be gone!
Oh my!
Did he just bring a leak?
All these ears are going to come out!
Enjoy the view.
It's your last.
Please, you know how to fly!
You scared the guts out of me!
The last two years were
a stain upon my soul.
Oh, Sanji!
I went through hell!
It isn't fair!
He got my ass!
I want to burn those days to ashes!
Hell, memory!
Scared the guts out of you?
Good, that'll make the job easier.
Blowfish guts are toxic.
You have to take that part out.
Let's see you block this!
Quit it, Frog.
This is over.
I told you I'm not a frog!
I'm the Master Swordsman Yasuie,
Fishman Islands Champion of
the Octopus Eight-Sword Style!
Curgatory!
PUNIGINI!
My mistake.
Maybe you're not a frog after all.
But you did broke.